import { Quiz, QuizQuestion } from '../../types';

const MyDayQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Opakujte v angličtině',
    name: 'Můj den',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['calendar'],
        question: 'kalendář'
      },
      {
        answer: ['exercise'],
        question: 'cvičit'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to stay'],
        question: 'zůstávat'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to perfume'],
        question: 'navonět se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to spend time'],
        question: 'trávit čas'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to put makeup on'],
        question: 'malovat se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['same'],
        question: 'stejný'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to meet'],
        question: 'scházet se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to feed'],
        question: 'nakrmit'
      },
      {
        answer: ['theater'],
        question: 'divadlo'
      },
      {
        answer: ['regularly'],
        question: 'pravidelně'
      },
      {
        answer: ['lazy'],
        question: 'líný'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to shower'],
        question: 'sprchovat se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['oat flakes'],
        question: 'ovesné vločky'
      },
      {
        answer: ['remove makeup'],
        question: 'odlíčit se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to get up'],
        question: 'vstávat'
      },
      {
        answer: ['alarm clock'],
        question: 'budík'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to shave'],
        question: 'holit se'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default MyDayQuiz;
